https://www.jayweller.com/contact/privacy-policy/

Protecting the privacy of your information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the JayWeller.com website and governs data collection and usage. By using the JayWeller.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. Collection of your Personal Information We may collect personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number only if you provide it to us in one of our online contact forms. If you purchase our services, we collect and store billing and credit card information. We may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your Postal Code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. We will not delete customer information for paying clientele unless explicitly asked to do so in writing. However, we reserve the right to delete customer information for clients at any time. Information about your computer hardware and software also may be automatically collected by JayWeller.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of our services, to maintain the quality of our services, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the our website. Communications between you and a participating attorney are confidential. For quality assurance purposes, and in order to deliver JayWeller.com services, we will have access to your communications with participating attorneys. JayWeller.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you visit so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Use of your Personal Information JayWeller.com does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. JayWeller.com may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. JayWeller.com may share your information with third parties who perform tasks required to complete a purchase transaction. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to JayWeller.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. JayWeller.com does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Clearwater Bankruptcy Law Office 25400 U.S. 19 North, Suite 215 Clearwater, FL 33763 Phone: 727-539-7701 Toll Free: 1-800-407-3328 (DEBT) Fax: 727-524-3850
Port Richey Bankruptcy Law Office BB&T BANK 9501 U.S. Highway 19 Suite 210 Port Richey, FL, 34668 Phone: 727-375-9378
Lakeland Bankruptcy Law Office 2614 Lakeland Hills Blvd, Ste 2 Lakeland, FL, 33805 Phone 863-802-5505
Tampa Law Office 4100 W. Kennedy Blvd., Suite 208 Tampa, FL 33609 Phone: 1-813-229-3328
© 2020. Weller Legal Group PA. All rights reserved.
Sitemap.
